http://www.promotionsnow.com/content/privacy

x
"message here"
Desktop Organizers
Glass/Crystal Boxes, Vases & Etc.
Stencils
Stickers, Balloons & Etc.
Privacy
At PromotionsNow.com, respecting your wishes about the information we collect from you is of great importance.
Personal information collection
We may collect the following kinds of personal information:
Information that you provide for the purpose of setting up an account on this website including your name, e-mail address, billing/shipping information and contact numbers
Information about transactions carried out over this website including products/quantities ordered and payment information.
Using personal information
We may use your personal information to:
Enable your access to and use of the website services.
Send to you products that you purchase.
Send to you statements and invoices.
Authorization and process credit card transactions.
Supply partner client with your name, address, phone number(s), and products/quantities ordered.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified above, we may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by this Company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.
SECURITY
Because your credit card security is our highest priority, PromotionsNow.com has taken several steps to ensure that your payment information is processed confidentially and accurately.
This protection provides a level of security that we are proud to offer.
Securing your data
We take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.
Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website is protected by encryption technology.
Transactions on the site are protected with up to 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer encryption.
Availability
The Company does not warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you thereby indemnify this Company, its employees, agents and affiliates against any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.
Refunds
Your customized order will be received free from defects and personalized as you requested, or we will replace your order or issue you a full refund, at our discretion.
Customized orders cannot be returned for refund for any other reasons. Your non-customized order may be returned for a refund, for any reason, minus shipping both ways. If your non-customized order is proven defective, we will also refund shipping charges both ways.
Delivery Process
Our preferred method of shipping is UPS Ground. For RUSH deliveries, we use alternate UPS and Federal Express services. Some of our products are in-stock and ready to ship from our Moorestown, NJ warehouse within 24 hours (excluding weekends and holidays).
All custom orders will require additional processing time and may ship from a location other than our local warehouse.
Analytics Tools
We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, such as Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies, to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online Sites and/or Services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.
The third party analytics companies who collect information on our Sites and/or Services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.
In addition to our use of technologies as described herein, we may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of Promotions Now Sites and/or Services and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of Promotions Now Sites and/or Services. For more information about this practice, please see the "Third Party Advertising Technologies" section below.
You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.
Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.
In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior.
These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products or placing advertisements, these third party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on any of our Sites and/or Services and on third party websites. Each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as indicated in this Policy. Please note this does not opt you out of being delivered advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Notification of Changes
The Company reserves the right to change these conditions at any time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement on a regular basis.
General
Redistribution or republication of any part of this site or its content is prohibited, including such by framing or other similar or any other means, without the express written consent of the Company.
Communication
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to: custserv@promotionsnow.com
These terms and conditions form part of the Agreement between the client and our company. Your accessing of this website indicates your understanding, agreement to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms and Conditions contained herein.
Terms and Conditions
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions and any or all Agreements: "Client", “You” and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the Company’s terms and conditions. "The Company", “Ourselves”, “We” and "Us", refers to PromotionsNow.com. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves. “Partner Client” refers to an organization for which we have created a website offering products customized for their organization.
SHOP
WHAT'S NEW
ON SALE
WHAT'S HOT!
SPECIALTY STORES
BRANDS
FREE SAMPLES
FEATURED COLLECTIONS
CUSTOMER SERVICE
MY ACCOUNT
CONTACT US
OUR GUARANTEE
Sales Team, 8 yrs
1270 Glen Avenue, Moorestown, NJ 08057 • 1-800-378-6376 | fax 1-800-528-4366
custserv@promotionsnow.com
© 2020 PromotionsNow.com
Free Samples
Free Art & Proof
Easy Payment
Easy Ordering
×
Ordering is Easy!
Our ordering options make it easier than ever to place your order with PromotionsNow.
Order online.
The steps shown in each product walk you right through the customization process. Your order will be processed by one of our inside sales reps who will make sure we get your final approval on an order acknowledgment and art proof before we go to print.
Order by phone.
Call us at 800.378.6376 and one of our inside sales reps will be happy to take your order and walk you through the process. Our reps are available 8:00am – 8:00pm Monday through Thursday and 8:00am – 7:00pm Friday (EST).
After Ordering
First, your order goes straight to your personal inside sales representative for review and troubleshooting. If there are questions, you will be contacted right away.
Next, we email you an order acknowledgment with any adjustment to charges or specifications, for your signature. This happens within 24 hours of receiving your order.
Finally, we email you a final art proof for your approval. If you have any changes, we'll make them promptly and send another proof for your approval. Your order will not go into production until you are completely satisfied with the artwork.
Thank you!
We know how important your order is.
You can trust us to take good care of it and you.
Close
×
Easy Payment!
Ordering is Easy! Place your order online or over the phone using any one of our easy payment methods.
Credit Card
We accept VISA, MasterCard and American Express.
Purchase Order
We're happy to accept all official purchase orders from accounts with already established credit. If ordering online, please select Purchase Order as payment method.
A copy can then be emailed or faxed to our office.
If you would like credit terms, you can discuss credit with your rep before or after your order is placed.
Check
If you prefer to make your payment later, please select Check when ordering online. We’ll get started on your order and let you know what type of payment arrangements are necessary to proceed.
We typically need a credit card on file or payment in advance for first time customers.
Need help with a purchase requisition?
Please call, email, or use the Request a Quote button on the items that you need for your purchase req. We'll email you a quote with all of the info you need to submit your purchase req the easy way.
Don't forget your tax-exempt number.
We charge sales tax in PA and NJ. Don't forget to put your tax exempt number in your order, or give it to your rep after you order, so we charge you accurately.
What else can we do to make ordering easier?
Let us know at custserv@promotionsnow.com
Close
×
Free Artwork and Art Proof!
On every custom item, you will receive a FREE art proof on your order. Your inside sales representative will send your artwork to our professional artists who will make sure your imprint fits perfectly on the item you have chosen. We will not proceed with production until you are satisfied.
Wondering how to send your artwork/logo?
Artwork can be sent via email to custserv@promotionsnow.com. From there we will make sure your art is sent to your inside sales representative. You can also attach art to your online order or email art directly to your sales rep.
We accept any artwork format for your order.
We can accept anything: e-mailed art, faxed art, or mailed hard copy. Just send us what you have and we’ll work with you on the rest.
Your art will be handled personally by a member of our design team. Your artist has the experience to make sure everything turns out just the way you want. Even though we prefer vector art, we can open virtually any file type.
Below are some of the most common file types with our suggestions:
Scans, faxes, web images, etc (JPG, PNG, SVG, TIF, GIF, BMP)
Send as is
Adobe Acrobat (PDF)
Suggested: Embed the fonts used or export as a generic EPS
Adobe Illustrator (AI, EPS)
Suggested: Convert text to outlines, embed any linked images
Adobe Photoshop (PSD)
Suggested: Convert text layers to shapes and embed any linked images
Microsoft Office Files (DOC, DOCX, PPT, PPTX, PUB)
Suggested: Embed or include fonts
Corel Draw (CDR)
Suggested: Convert text to curves
If you don’t see your file type above, don’t worry. Send us what you have and we’ll let you know if we need anything else before we proceed.
Close
×
Free Samples!
Requesting samples is now even more convenient!
We are happy to send samples free of charge to any legitimate business or organization in the United States. Free samples are provided to existing and potential customers and are not for personal use. All businesses are verified with Dun & Bradstreet. Business who cannot be verified may be offered the option to purchase samples at a discount, with any sample charges refunded on orders of $250.00 or more. We cannot ship free samples to home addresses or unverified businesses/organizations.
For samples to Canada or other destinations outside of the US, please provide your shipper number so we can ship on your freight account.
For sample requests totaling more than $10.00, a representative may contact you. We may ask that more expensive samples be returned to us - but that's free of charge too. We'll include instructions on how to get them back to us when you're finished. Special order samples may need to be purchased, at a discount, refundable on your subsequent order. We'll let you know what we need to proceed.
Request online!
On each product page there is a Request a Free Sample button. Select it to add an item to your sample basket.
Continue to browse through products and add samples to your basket as you need.
When you are ready to finalize your sample order, just click on the Sample Basket link at the top of any page. Once you are in your sample basket, you may remove any unnecessary samples, if you like.
Then select the Request Samples button. Your request will be received by a representative shortly.
You must check out your sample basket in order to receive your requested samples.
Thank you!
Thank you so much for considering PromotionsNow for your next promotional product order. Our job is to make your job easier.
If you prefer to talk to a representative, call 1.800.378.6376 to place your sample request over the phone.
This is my:
Home Address
Business Address
Phone
Email address
Thank You!
Your request for a catalog has been sent. You will receive your catalog within 5 to 7 business days.
Sign in to access your account.
Forgot password?
Login
New Customer
Enter your email address and we’ll register you.
Create Account
Cancel
×
